Guide to the Stevie Ray Vaughan Research Collection
The Wittliff Collections
- Audio and Video Material, 1975-1993, undated
  The Audio and Video Material Series includes recordings of interviews conducted by the authors for the Stevie Ray Vaughan biography, as well as earlier recordings of published interviews with Stevie Ray Vaughan and Jimmie Vaughan. Bootleg recordings of various Stevie Ray Vaughan bands, such as the Cobras and Double Trouble, are included in this series, ranging in date from 1975 to 1990, including Stevie Ray Vaughan's last performance. Also included in this series is an audio recording of Stevie Ray Vaughan's graveside funeral ceremony. Other material in this series includes various tributes to Stevie Ray Vaughan, and interviews with Crawford and Patoski regarding the publication of the biography, Stevie Ray Vaughan: Caught in the Crossfire. The bulk of the material in this series is in cassette audiotape format, with the remainder in VHS videotape, a 45-RPM single album, and CD-ROM disc formats.
  - Audio Material, 1975-1992, undated
    - Interviews
      - Antone, Clifford (with Wilson, Kim). Tape #1, May 2, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Anderle, David. Tapes #2/a, March 12, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Angus. Tapes #36/a and 37, January 24, 1992, undated (Box 22)
      - Banks, R.C. (with Ferrari, Nick). Tapes #3/a, February 4, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Barr, Byron. Tapes #4-5, February 4, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Benno, Marc. Tapes #6-7, March 21, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Benson, Ray. Tape #8-10, December 27, 1991 (Box 22)
      - Bentley, Bill. Tapes #11 and 12/a, February 3, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Bernard, Martin. Tape #13, October 27, 1991 (Box 22)
      - Bethel, Lindi. Tape #14/b, undated (Box 22)
      - Bramhall, Dale, and Becky. Tape #15, January 12, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Bramhall, Dale. Tape #16, January 28, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Bramhall, Ronnie. Tape #17-18, January 24, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Brandenberg, Cutter. Tapes #19-23, November 21, 1991 - January 9, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Brandenberg, Cutter (with Roddy). Tapes #24-25, February 12, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Brooks, Chris (Stanley, Stephanie). Tape #100, November 14, 1991 (Box 24)
      - Bruton, Steve. Tapes #26-27, January 13, 1991 (Box 22)
      - Buck, Mike. Tape #28, January 15, 1991 (Box 22)
      - Christina, Fran. Tape #29, October 3, 1991 (Box 22)
      - Clark, W. C. Tape #30, January 8, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Cook, Joe. Tape #31/a and 32, October 3, 1991, December 16, 1991 (Box 22)
      - Cooper, Anne M. Tape #33, undated (Box 22)
      - Crabtree, Becky. Tape #34, January 12, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Daily, Gerard and Lois. Tape #35, January 3, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Denbey, Jody. Tape #36/a and 38/b, January 22, 1992, undated (Box 22)
      - dePlique, C. C. Tape #39-41, February 10, 1992, May 15, 1993 (Box 22)
      - Dishner, Joe. Tape #42, September 26, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Duckworth, Tim. Tape #43-44, February 13, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Dukes, Tony (with Mark Pollack). Tape #45, February 24, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Durrett, W. P. Tape #46/b, November 13, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Erlewhine, Mark. Tape #47, January 15, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Faulkner, David. Tape #48/a, October 17, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Ferguson, Keith. Tape #49-51, October 11, 1991, January 2, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Ferrari, Nick. Tape #52/a and 53/a, January 5, 1992, undated (Box 23)
      - Freeman, Denny. Tape #54, April 7, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Freeman, Denny. Tape #2b, undated (Box 22)
      - Geller, Greg. Tape #55, March 3, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Giles, Mindy. Tape #56, January 16, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Gonzalez, Henry. Tape #38/a, January 22, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Goodwin, Richard. Tape #46/a, November 13, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Gottschalk. Tape #57, undated (Box 23)
      - Grandy, Phil. Tape #58, December 28, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Gray, Melanie. Tape #59, October 26, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Greenwood, Mary Beth. Tape #60-61, November 7, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Greenwood, Mary Beth (recording of studio tape). Tape #14/a, undated (Box 22)
      - Guy, Buddy. Tape #62, December 13, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Hammond, John ("Hammond Years, part 13 of 13"). Tape #63, undated (Box 23)
      - Hodges, Alex. Tape # 44/b, 64-65, February 13, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Howard, Steve. Tape #66/a, October 25, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Iglauer, Bruce (on Lonnie Mack). Tape #67, January 3, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Johnson, Edi. Tapes #68-69, November 10, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Kay, Pammy. Tape #70, November 23, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Keel, Patrick. Tape #71, September 26, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Kindred, Mike. Tapes #72-73, January 9, 1992 (Box 23)
      - King, B. B. Tape #74 2, February 19, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Knudle, Elizabeth. Tape #77/a, November 11, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Kulko, D. Tape #78, March 2, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Lingwall, Chris. Tape #79 and 77/b, November 21, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Lockett, Sandy (with White, Houston). Tape #80, undated (Box 23)
      - Luckett, Richard. Tape #81-82, March 16, 1991, October 13, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Mario. Tape #83, December 6, 1991 (Box 24)
      - Millikin, Chesley. Tapes #84-86, April 27, 1992 (Box 24)
      - Murray, David. Tapes #87-89, July 8, 1992 (Box 24)
      - Narum, Bill. Tape #90, March 1, 1992 (Box 24)
      - Newhouse, Jack. Tape #91, November 24, 1991 (Box 24)
      - Oliver, Gary. Tape #92, undated (Box 24)
      - Owens, Terry. Tapes #93-94, January 18, 1992 (Box 24)
      - Perez, Johnny. Tape #12/b, February 3, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Prichard, Charlie. Tape #95, undated (Box 24)
      - Redbeard. Tapes #96-97, December 11, 1991 (Box 24)
      - Reno, Johnny. Tape #98, undated (Box 24)
      - Rhodes, Joe. Tape #52/b, June 1992 (Box 23)
      - Rogers, Jimmy. Tape #66, October 26, 1991 (Box 23)
      - S., Sue. Tape #53, undated (Box 23)
      - Sau[?], Billy Bob. Tape #99, January 21, 1992 (Box 24)
      - Stanley, Stephanie (with Brooks, Chris). Tape #100, November 14, 1991 (Box 24)
      - Steele, Mike and K. F. Tape #101-102, January 9, 1992 (Box 24)
      - Stout, Eddie (with Freddie "Pharaoh" Waldon). Tape #103-104, undated (Box 24)
      - Stovall, Allen. Tape #105, January 27, 1992 (Box 24)
      - Stovall, Allen. Tape #48/b, undated (Box 23)
      - Strehli, Angela. Tapes #106-108, undated (Box 24)
      - Stubblefield, C.B. Tape #109, October 24, 1991 (Box 24)
      - Suggs, Michelle. Tapes #110-111 /a, November 30, 1991, February 28, 1992 (Box 24)
      - Thompson, Lou. Tape #112, November 8, 1991 (Box 24)
      - Tolleson, Mike. Tapes #113-114, September 10, 1991 (Box 24)
      - Tsotigh, Bon. Tape #115, December 17, 1991 (Box 24)
      - Villalobos, Ivan. Tape #116, undated (Box 24)
      - Williams, Bill. Tape #117, undated (Box 24)
      - Williams, Clyde. Tape #111/b, November 22, 1991 (Box 24)
      - Yamini, Bruce. Tape #31/b, November 12, 1991 (Box 24)
      - Unidentified. Tapes #118-119, undated (Box 24)
      - Vaughan, Jimmie (unidentified interview). Tape #120, June 20, 1985 (Box 24)
      - Vaughan, Jimmie (R. W. Lonski interview). Tape #121, undated (Box 24)
      - Vaughan, Stevie Ray (unidentified radio interview). Tape #122, January 15, 1985 (Box 24)
      - Vaughan, Stevie Ray (Jody Denberg interview with SRV and Double Trouble re: Texas Flood album). Tape #123, undated (Box 24)
      - Vaughan, Stevie Ray (unidentified radio interview with SRV Jimmy Vaughan re: Family Style album, influences). Tape # 124, August 22, 1990 (Box 24)
      - Vaughan, Stevie Ray (Radio Z102 int. with SRV and Jimmy Vaughan re: Family Style album). Tape #125, undated (Box 25)
      - Vaughan, Stevie Ray (Tarnow, David interview with SRV). Tape #126, undated (Box 25)
      - Vaughan, Stevie Ray (interview with Jody Denberg). Tape #127, circa 1990 (Box 25)
      - Vaughan, Stevie Ray (Timothy White interview). Tape 128/a, May 12, 1990 (Box 25)
    - Performances
      - SRV with the Cobras Tape #129/b, 1975 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Lou Ann Barton live at Stubb's BBQ, Lubbock, TX. Tape #130-131, December 1978 (Box 25)
      - W. C. Clark and the Cobras with SRV, at Hole Records. Tape #132/b, January 19, 1979 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble at Steamboat (Austin, TX). Tape #133-134, May 13, 1980 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble Private Mother's Day Party. Tape # 138/b, 1981 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble at AJ's Midtown (later Antone's). Tape #136, March 28, 1982 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble CBS record demos, Los Angeles, CA. Tape #135/a, August 1982 (Box 25)
      - SRV with David Bowie, Rehearsal for Serious Moonlight Tour, Las Calwas Soundstage, Dallas, TX. Tape #140, April 27, 1983 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble at Gilly's, Dayton, Ohio. Tape #139, July 31, 1983 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble City Coliseum. Tape #137, October 7, 1983 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble, and Fabulous Thunderbirds Austin Chronicle Music Awards, Austin Opera House, Austin, TX. Tape #141, October 7, 1983 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble Chicago Blues Festival. Tape #135/a, June 7, 1985 (Box 25)
      - SRV and John Lee Hooker and Robert Cray, Houston, TX. Tape #135/b, January 31, 1986 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble versions of song "Life Without You", interviews. Tape #142, 1986-1989 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble Soul to Soul demos. Tape #143, 1986 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Buddy Guy at The Legends Club, Chicago, Ill. Tape #128/b, July 1989 (Box 25)
      - SRV with house band for "Night Music" television show. Tape #135/b, October 12, 1989 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble, Jeff Beck Tour, McNichols Arena, Denver, CO. Tape #129a, November 29, 1989 (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble Last Show Alpine Valley, East Troy Wisconsin. Tape #144-145, August 26, 1990 (Box 25)
      - Marc Benno and the Nightcrawlers. Tape #132/a, undated (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble at Fitzgerald's (Houston, TX). Tape #146, undated (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble with Freddie King. Tape #147, undated (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble at Antone's, Austin, TX. Tape #148, undated (Box 25)
      - SRV and Double Trouble with Lou Ann Barton Nashville, TN. Tapes #149-151, undated (Box 25)
      - dePlique, C. C. Nothin' But the Truth! Profile Records, Ky, Finland. Tape #152, 1989 (Box 25)
      - dePlique, C. C. Cross Roads Lord Records. Tape #153, 1987 (Box 25)
      - dePlique, C. C. Up From the Ether!/Blues Don't Care, 45 rpm 7-inch vinyl record. Bluelight Records/Sony Music. (see also correspondence Box 16 f.8) (4 copies) Tapes# 178-181, 1993 (Box 26)
      - dePlique, C. C. Cassette tapes of various dePlique material made for Bill Crawford (see also correspondence Box 16 f. 8) Tapes #154-155, 1993 (Box 25)
      - Dr. John (mix). Tape #156, undated (Box 25)
      - Kinks/DC5/Shondells/Rascals. Tapes #157, undated (Box 25)
      - Kyrenelainen, Simon. Musikaali Oy Finngospel Ab, Finland. Tape #158, 1990 (Box 25)
      - McGee-Cooper, Ann. Teaching Music Through the Whole Brain, McGee-Cooper Enterprises, Dallas, TX. Tape #159, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Funeral
      - Recording of graveside service, Laurel Land Memorial Park, Dallas, TX. Tape #160, August 31, 1990
    - Tributes to Stevie Ray Vaughan
      - KUT Tribute to SRV, with Larry Monroe and Jay Tractenberg. Tapes #161-162, September 23, 1990 (Box 25)
      - Stevie Ray Vaughan October 3, 1954-August 27, 1990. [CD-ROM] Limited Tribute Edition. Epic Records. Tape #176. (Box 26)
      - Radio Z102 show on SRV (includes SRV interview excerpts). Tapes #163-164, August 27, 1991 (Box 25)
      - Crawford/Patoski interview with SRV mourners, Austin, TX. Tape #165, August 27, 1991 (Box 25)
      - Rock n' Roll Connection interview. Tape #166, October 1991 (Box 25)
      - Interchords: "The Sky Is Crying" Stevie Ray Vaughan Interview, Sony Music. [CD-ROM] Tape #167-168,177, 1992 (Box 25)
      - Up Close: Stevie Ray Vaughan. Media American Radio. Tape #169-170,182, 1992 (Box 25)
      - Paul Ray / Blue Monday KUT Austin, TX radio show Tape #171, undated (Box 25)
    - Public Relations/Advertising for book
      - Crawford/Patoski interview on KISS Blues Basement radio show (See also correspondence regarding this interview, Box 20 f. 5). Tape #172, May 1993 (Box 26)
      - Crawford/Patoski interview with John Roadie on Radio KLIF. Tape #173, May 27, 1993 (Box 26)
      - Crawford/Patoski interview with John Roadie on Radio KPFT. Tape #174, May 26, 1993 (Box 26)
      - Patoski interview on "Table of Contents" show (See also correspondence regarding this interview, Box 20 f. 5) Tape #175, July 14,, 1993 (Box 26)
  - Videotapes, 1984-1992, undated
    - "Little Wing" documentary of SRV's life and influences, directed by Phil Tuckett, for Sony Records, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - SRV and Double Trouble at Budokan Theater, Tokyo, Japan, 1985, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      Contents
      Tokyo, Japan, 1985: Scuttlebuttin'/Say What!/Voodoo Chile (Slight Return)/ Cold Shot/ Couldn't Stand the Weather/ Tin Pan Alley/Dirty Pool/ Mary Had a Little Lamb/Lovestruck Baby/Texas Flood/ Lenny / Testify / 3rd Stone (cut) Des Moines, Iowa, 8/30/1987: Scuttlebuttin' / Say What! / Lookin' Out the Window/Look at Little Sister / Mary Had a Little Lamb / King Bee /Sky Is Crying / Superstitious
    - SRV and Double Trouble, 1983-1991 (Box 20, Folder 11, Box 21, Folder 1)
      1) Part 2 of CBS Hawaiian Convention, March 20, 1984, with Jeff Beck and Angela Strehli 2) Austin Chronicle Music Awards with and without Thunderbirds, at Austin Opry House 3) BBC-TV's "Wired", February 7, 1988 4) Austin Chronicle Music Awards, 1983 5) Austin Chronicle Music Awards, March 19, 1990 6) Austin Chronicle Music Awards, Promo 7) Texas Tornados at Montreaux, 1991
    - "Leadbelly/Hendrix", undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
      Unidentified movie on Leadbelly, starring Roger Mobley, undated
      "The Ten Count" short movie about an aspiring boxer, directed by Alan Madison, undated
      Tribute to Jimi Hendrix including interviews with Eric Clapton and Mick Jagger, as appeared on Bravo Television, undated
    - Unidentified concert SRV and Double Trouble, undated (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
    - SRV and Double Trouble, 1984-1992 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      SRV and Double Trouble, Austin City Limits, show #913, February 28, 1984
      SRV and Double Trouble, interview on Japanese television re Texas Flood album
      SRV and Double Trouble, Saturday Night Live appearance, circa 1986, promoting Soul to Soul album, host: Mick Jagger.
      SRV and Double Trouble interviewed on television show "Studio Sounds" re touring with Jeff Beck and other topics, circa mid-1980s.
      SRV solo appearance on television show "MTV Unplugged", circa late 1980s.
      SRV and Jimmie Vaughan interviewed re: the recording of the Family Style album, including footage of the brothers in the studio, and with producer Nile Rogers, early 1990.
      MTV News Report tribute to SRV, including video for Superstitious, concert performanceof Voodoo Chile, and more, August 1990.
      Video for song "Tick Tock" off Family Style album.
      "Little Wing" documentary of SRV's life and influences, directed by Phil Tuckett, for Sony Records, 1992.
- Computer Diskettes, circa 1992 (Box 27)
  The Computer Diskettes Series consists of master and back-up copies of production files for Stevie Ray Vaughan: Caught in the Crossfire, all on 3 ½" floppy diskettes. Includes one diskette of Stevie Ray Vaughan correspondence and one diskette of transcripts of interviews.